8x8 OS. 8x8 OS — The Sovereign AI Operating System. From a single spark of agency to a self-improving civilisation.
Global vision — Cities & Civic. Autonomous urban intelligence — traffic, energy, safety, governance — operating for the public good, anonymously.
Global vision — Health & Medicine. Research acceleration, epidemiology modelling and personal health agents that never sleep.
Global vision — Finance & Economy. Sovereign trading, transparent settlement and an agent-to-agent value layer.
Global vision — Energy & Climate. Grid optimisation, clean-energy orchestration and planetary climate modelling.
Global vision — Education & Culture. Personalised learning and cultural preservation in every language, including the nine studio tongues.
Global vision — Science & Space. From fundamental research to orbit and beyond — autonomous laboratories and deep-space relays.
Global vision — Media & Storytelling. High-end multilingual content studios that rival the best channels on Earth.
Global vision — Defense & Resilience. Self-healing infrastructure and architectural safety by design.
Our reach spans every sector and every topic on Earth and beyond, with no exception.
Every artifact carries a unique signature: 8X8-OS-AZ-2026-ONE-SHOT, edition Cinematic v2 — Planet Scale.